







Current Designation: Technical Lead Total Experience: 16 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Avaya Pvt. Ltd Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science]

Pref. Location: Hyderabad, Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Technical Lead, Team Lead, Software Application, Software Development, Technical Architecture, Application Support, Product Implementation, Stakeholder/ Client Engagement, Java, Shell Scripting, JUnit, Mockito, Jira, Crucible

Verified : L Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

## Summary

Atechnical professional offering 14.5 years of experience in designing & developing applications/ products in Java/ J2EE Technologies, managing various technical projects and rendering support in devising strategies, objectives, vision & roadmap

Rich & qualitative experience in managing complete SDLC including development, enhancements, customization, requirement gathering & analysis, design, testing, UAT, customer support and training

Currently working as Technical Lead and facilitating the creation and deployment of solutions that are scalable, secure and aligned with company-wide business and IT objectives

Domain expertise entails Telecom (Contact Center, NMS, EMS, OSS) and Performance Domain

Excellence in understanding requirements of clients & other multiple stakeholders, followed by translation into functional specifications as well as provisioning of suitable software solutions

Strong project management experience with skills in implementing Agile & Waterfall

### **Work Experience**

- Avaya Pvt. Ltd as Technical Lead Oct 2014 to Till Date
- Wipro Technologies as Technical Lead Sep 2007 to Oct 2014
- BMC Software (Proactive Net) as Product Developer Feb 2006 to Sep 2007

^ Back to Top

### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science) from U. V. Patel College of Engineering, Hemchandracharya North Gujarat University in 2003

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Sun Certified Java Programming (Java5)

^ Back to Top

### IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

# **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

JAVA, Shell Scripting
SQL & C
PostgreSQL, MySQL
Intersystem Cache, Oracle & SQL Server
Java-J2EE, Spring Framework
Spring Boot, JavaScript & HTML5
Linux, HP/UX, Win 10
Win 2008 Server & Win 2012 Server
Tomcat, WebSphere & NGINX
Git, Bitbucket, SVN & Rational ClearCase
Sonar, Coverity, Findbugs
CODEPRO
JaCoCo & Karma Runner
JUnit, Mockito, Jasmin & Grunt
Jira & Rational Clearquest
Maven, ANT and make
crucible
JConsole, JMap, VisualVM
JMC, JProfiler & Your Kit
Agile & Waterfall

^ Back to Top

# **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No** 

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.